Finding Aid for Health Science Relations (University of Michigan)scrapbooks, 1958-1974
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Health Science Relations (University of Michigan) scrapbooks 1958-1974
University of Michigan. Health Science Relations.
1 linear foot and 5 oversize volumes
87176 BImu Bimu C501 2
Scrapbooks, 1958-1974, of Health Science Relations of the University of Michigan, agency concerned with the distribution of news relating to health care delivery and research. Include clippings of news stories relating, in part, to the University of Michigan Medical School and Hospital.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The scrapbooks were received from donor no. 6661.
The record group is open without restriction.
Health Science Relations of the University of Michigan was concerned with the distribution of news relating to health care delivery and research.
The Health Science Relations scrapbooks include clippings of news stories relating, in part, to the University of Michigan Medical School and Hospital.
Subjects:
Medicine--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; University of Michigan. Medical School.; University of Michigan. University Hospital.
Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.
- Scrapbooks
  - 1958-1960 (Volume 1)
  - 1961-1963 (Volume 2)
  - 1963-1965 (Volume 3)
  - 1965-1969 (Volume 4)
  - 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 1)
  - 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Regarding Services of Health Science Relations (Volume 5)